FASESIN MATHEW

GRAPHICS DESIGNER/ MARKETING STRATEGIST

CONTACT

- 19, Adebiyi Street, Shomolu, Lagos, Nigeria.
- fasesinolayiwolamathe w@gmail.com
- 08146289500
- in http://linkedin.com/in/m athew-fasesinbb0b66186

PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly creative and multi-talented Graphic Designer/ Digital Marketer/ with extensive experience Marketing, Graphics design, multimedia and printing. To work with passion, sincerity and diligence for the improvement of the organization in a position which will effectively and efficiently display my transferrable skills (Marketing, graphics design, set design, project management and consultancy (Building and housing construction) and also meet set target, improve and impact society positively.

TECH SKILLS

- CorelDraw
- Photoshop
- Power Point
- Microsoft Word
- Canva
- Affter Effect

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Language: Fluent in English and Yoruba
- Leadership
- High level of attention to details
- Planning, Scheduling, Controlling.
- High level of Integrity and Discipline
- Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- Proactive and goal oriented,
- Project Management (Building)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphics Executor/ Digital Marketer Rave TV, Ilupeju, Lagos

JUNE 2019-PRESENT

- Successfully manage and coordinate graphic design and different shows set design projects from concept through completion.
- Work closely with the marketing team to drive effective execution of BTL marketing activities.
- Contributed to the planning and generation of the montly activation schedule
- Design proposals for highly persuasive sales and marketing presentations.
- Successfully created a trademark for the brand.
- Provide layouts and templates for programs.
- Establish relationships with other media firm designers

Graphics Designer, Liberty Prints + Media Institute, Ojo, Lagos.

APRIL 2015 - MARCH 2019

- Completed and maintained accurate records or reports regarding the operations progress of the company's systems.
- Coordinated graphics design project

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

B.A (Theatre Arts and Music)

Lagos State University, Ojo.

2008 - 2014

Senior School Certificate Examination

LillyFields Comprehensive College, Ejigbo, Lagos

HOBBIES/INTEREST

- TRAVELING/ADVENTURING,
- SOCIAL NETWORKING.
- · READING,
- TECH. HOBBIES (COMPUTING),
- POLITICS.
- ART, MUSIC (PLAYING, LISTENING)
- TEAM SPORTS (FOOTBALL)
- HOUSING AND CONSTRUCTION

Large Format and Monogram Operator, Harrymade Prints, Abraham Adesanya Complex, Shomolu, Lagos.

JULY-DECEMBER 2014

- Printed and made copies of work.
- Performed routine maintenance and repairs on printing machines.
- Attended special training sessions to increase knowledge and skills.
- Inspected samples at random during prints runs to identify any errors.
- Responsible for the safe and confidential handling of client's work.
- Ensured machine prints meet the highest quality expectations of clients.

Clerk,

Tunde Bright Enterprises, Shomolu, Lagos.

SEPTEMBER 2010 - JUNE 2012

- Archived complete documents on computer hard drive or disk, and/or maintained a computer filing system to store, retrieve, update and delete documents.
- Printed and made copies of work.
- Manually collated pages of reports and other documents prepared.

A C H I E V E M E N T S / C E R T I F I C A T I O N S

- Brand Activation for RaveTV youth Alive with LUSH HAIR (Games Night)- 2021
- RaveTV Staff of the Quarter 2020-2021
- Brand Activation for Banter Better with Coca cola 2019
- Lagos State Readysetwork 2018 (Scholar)
- Creative Team Lead for KIDZ GOT MOVES with Indomie 2018
- DigifyNG 2018 (digital marketing skills)
- Students representative for digifyng in LASU (Ambassador)
- Faculty of Arts @ 25 2018 (Organizing Chairman)
- Brand Activation for LACASERA Drink for Miss LASU Beauty Pageant 2018
- Nigerian Universities Theatre Arts Festival 2017 (Association international des-critiques de theatre international association of theatre critics certification)
- British Council Theatre Festival 2017 (Marketer)
- Faculty of Arts Students Association (Entrepreneur of the Year 2017 & 2018)
- Faculty of Arts Students Association (P. R. O 2017)
- Association of Theatre Arts Students, Lagos State University (Assistant P. R. O 2016)